<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Introduction on Threat Hunting Toolkit</title><link>https://ethack.github.io/tht/</link><description>Recent content in Introduction on Threat Hunting Toolkit</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 May 2021 08:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ethack.github.io/tht/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Filter</title><link>https://ethack.github.io/tht/filter/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 May 2021 11:07:35 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://ethack.github.io/tht/filter/</guid><description>Here is an overview of the pages in this category:
Chop Like `cut` but with column names and CSV/TSV/JSON/Zeek support without the boilerplate. Filter Parallel searching for IPs, domains, or regexes across [un]compressed logs. Plus special features for Zeek logs. ug - Ugrep rg - Ripgrep grepcidr json-cut - Like zeek-cut but for JSON logs.</description></item><item><title>Summarize</title><link>https://ethack.github.io/tht/summarize/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 May 2021 11:07:50 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://ethack.github.io/tht/summarize/</guid><description>Here is an overview of the pages in this category:
Conn Summary Output a summary of connections given an input of Zeek logs. Great for getting an overview of a subset of logs. distinct - Outputs unique lines. count - Counts number of lines. card - Counts unique lines, printing the cardinality of the data. freq - Displays the number of occurrences, or frequency, of each unique line. mfo - Most Frequent Occurrence.</description></item><item><title>Correlate</title><link>https://ethack.github.io/tht/correlate/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 May 2021 11:07:27 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://ethack.github.io/tht/correlate/</guid><description>Here is an overview of the pages in this category:
zannotate dog mtr whois whois-bulk</description></item><item><title>Visualize</title><link>https://ethack.github.io/tht/visualize/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 May 2021 11:08:08 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://ethack.github.io/tht/visualize/</guid><description>Here is an overview of the pages in this category:
bat - Like cat but with line numbers, syntax highlighting, and scrolling. pxl - Display images in the terminal. Useful if you generate a chart and save it as an image. pv - Show a progress bar for long-running commands. plot-bar - Displays a bar chart in the terminal. zv, cv, tv - Zeek viewer, CSV viewer, TSV viewer will give you a scrollable table view of your data.</description></item><item><title>Multipurpose</title><link>https://ethack.github.io/tht/multipurpose/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 May 2021 11:07:40 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://ethack.github.io/tht/multipurpose/</guid><description>Here is an overview of the pages in this category:
miller xsv tsv-utils zq jq</description></item><item><title>Utils</title><link>https://ethack.github.io/tht/utils/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 May 2021 11:07:55 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://ethack.github.io/tht/utils/</guid><description>Here is an overview of the pages in this category:
domain - Will truncate a full domain to a given number of subdomains (default 2). ts2 - Convert timestamps between different formats. dust - File size analyzer. entr - File change watcher. fd - File finder. Like find but better. fzf - Fuzzy finder. htop - System resource viewer. Like top but prettier. hyperfine - Benchmarking tool. Like time but more powerful.</description></item><item><title>Development</title><link>https://ethack.github.io/tht/development/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ethack.github.io/tht/development/</guid><description>Running Clone the THT repo.
git clone https://github.com/ethack/tht.git Then run THT in development mode.
cd tht ./tht --dev This mounts certain files from this repository directly into the container which allows making changes to scripts without having to rebuild the image.
Building Docker Image You can build the image manually with the following command. However, the Maxmind geo information will not be included.
docker build -t ethack/tht . If you want to build with Maxmind data, you&amp;rsquo;ll need to sign up for a free Maxmind license key.</description></item></channel></rss>